Guide to the Donald M. Goldstein Collection, 1886-2005 UA.90.F78
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- 2013 Additions, XVI
  - Oversized Materials, 11.
    This subseries contains oversized materials that have been removed from the previous subsections in this series for easier storage. Of particular note, this subseries contains a framed photograph of the Japanese surrender on the USS Missouri signed by Admiral Nimitz and addressed to Gordon Prange. In addition, this subseries also contains a bobblehead of Donald Goldstein's likeness.
    - Air Craft Recognition Playing Cards, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Framed Notes, Given to George W. Prange by Admiral Nimitz, Undated (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Framed Photograph of the Japanese Surrender on the USS Missouri, Signed by Admiral Nimitz, Undated (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Goldstein Bobblehead Doll (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Goldstein, Hampton Highschool Yearbook, 1949 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Goldstein, Personal Photo Album, Undated (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Goldstein, Sigma Nu Photographs, Framed, 1954 (Box 7)
    - Goldstein, University of Maryland Yearbook, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Henry Ford, Undated (Box 7, Folder 9)